---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&category=27
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Faraday v2.6.0
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sat, 05 Nov 2022 17:45:31 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=7286ea9896f7f5f7fd4f6e5fa6ab716e; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        is the fastest  land animal?","correct_answer":"Cheetah","incorrect_answers":["Lion","Thomson&rsquo;s
        Gazelle","Pronghorn Antelope"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        color\/colour is a polar bear&#039;s skin?","correct_answer":"Black","incorrect_answers":["White","Pink","Green"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"For
        what reason would a spotted hyena &quot;laugh&quot;?","correct_answer":"Nervousness","incorrect_answers":["Excitement","Aggression","Exhaustion"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"The
        Platypus is a mammal.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the name of the family that the domestic cat is a member of?","correct_answer":"Felidae","incorrect_answers":["Felinae","Felis","Cat"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the name of the copper-rich protein that creates the blue blood in the
        Antarctic octopus?","correct_answer":"Hemocyanin","incorrect_answers":["Cytochrome","Iron","Methionine"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which
        of these is a colony of polyps and not a jellyfish?","correct_answer":"Portuguese
        Man-of-War","incorrect_answers":["Sea Wasp","Irukandji","Sea Nettle"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The
        internet browser Firefox is named after the Red Panda.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"To
        which biological phylum do all mammals, birds and reptiles belong?","correct_answer":"Chordata","incorrect_answers":["Echinodermata","Annelida","Placazoa"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the world&#039;s longest venomous snake?","correct_answer":"King Cobra","incorrect_answers":["Green
        Anaconda","Inland Taipan","Yellow Bellied Sea Snake"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sat, 05 Nov 2022 17:45:31 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
